http://www.siegelgale.com/privacy-policy

SIEGEL+GALE: COOKIE POLICY
Effective Date: 15th August, 2020
Siegel+Gale respects your concerns about privacy. We obtain certain information by automated means, such as cookies, web server logs, web beacons, and other technologies (collectively “Cookies”) when you visit, access, or use our websites, mobile sites or applications, that link to this Cookie Policy (collectively the “Sites”). This Cookie Policy explains how we use Cookies, their purposes, and how you can control them. Our use of Cookies may involve the processing of personal information. For more information on our data protection practices, see our Privacy Policy.
Click on one of the links below to jump to the listed section:
What are Cookies?
What Information Do We Obtain Through Cookies?
Cookies Used on Our Sites
Essential Cookies
Functional Cookies
Analytics Cookies
Social Media Cookies
Your Choices
Contact Us
What are Cookies?
A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. This technology helps us [(1) remember your information so you will not have to re-enter it; (2) track and understand how you use and interact with the Site; (3) tailor the Site around your preferences; (4) measure the usability of the Site; (5) understand the effectiveness of our communications; and (6) otherwise manage and enhance the Site].
What Information Do We Obtain Through Cookies?
The information we obtain in this manner includes [your device IP address, domain name, identifiers associated with your devices, device and operating system type and characteristics, web browser characteristics, language preferences, clickstream data, your interactions with the Sites (such as the web pages you visit, links you click and features you use), the pages that led or referred you to the Sites, dates and times of access to the Sites, and other information about your use of the Sites].
Cookies Used on Our Sites
Below is a list of the Cookies that we use on our Sites. You can indicate your choices with respect to the use of Cookies via the Cookie preferences center tab available on the left side of the screen. Please note that, depending on your selection, you may not be able to take full advantage of the Sites or our products and services.
Essential Cookies
These Cookies are essential to use and navigate our Sites. Essential Cookies help us collect information, such as [your session ID and other server information that enables us to authenticate users]. Essential Cookies are deleted when you end your browsing session or within a short period of time thereafter.
Name of Cookie
Purpose of Use
Duration
NA
NA
NA
Functional Cookies
These Cookies collect information about your choices or remember your preferences so we can show you content you requested. They allow us to [identify your location and remember your language during a browsing session and to customize the Sites you have accessed].
wp9371
This cookie is set to submit the Contact Us form.
One Year
f24_autoId
This cookie is saved while submitting the Contact Us form for marketing automation with Force24.
Valid upto 30th August, 2030
f24_personId
This cookie is saved while submitting the Contact Us form for marketing automation with Force24.
Valid upto 30th August, 2030
CookieLawInfoConsent
The cookie is used to store the summary of the consent given for cookie usage. It does not store any personal information.
1 Year
viewed_cookie_policy
The cookie is used to store whether or not you have consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data.
1 Year
cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary
The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not you have given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category ‘Necessary’.
1 Year
cookielawinfo-checkbox-non-necessary
The purpose of this cookie is to check whether or not you have given the consent to the usage of cookies under the category ‘Non-Necessary’.
1 Year
Analytics Cookies
We use analytics Cookies to collect information on [how users navigate and use our Sites, such as how the users traverse our Sites, the pages they view, which links they choose to click, how long they stay on a page, which page they are on when leaving the Sites and whether the page is displayed correctly or whether errors occur]. We also use analytics Cookies to [present users with feedback polls regarding their experience on our Sites]. Such cookies help us to [improve the performance of our Sites, make the Sites more user-friendly and build, maintain and improve our Sites with user feedback]. Some of these Cookies are persistent Cookies which remain on your computer or other Internet-connected device for a certain period of time after you end your browsing session, unless you delete them. These Cookies are provided by third-party analytics providers, including [Google and Hotjar]. For more information about these third-party providers’ Cookies, please click on the link below:
Google Analytics
Google Tag Manager
Hotjar
The following analytics Cookies are used on our Sites:
Name of Cookie
Purpose of Use
Duration
_ga
This cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to calculate visitor, session, camapign data and keep track of site usage for the site’s analytics report. The cookies store information anonymously and assigns a randoly generated number to identify unique visitors.
2 Years
_gid
This cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to store information of how visitors use a website and helps in creating an analytics report of how the wbsite is doing. The data collected including the number visitors, the source where they have come from, and the pages viisted in an anonymous form.
24 Hours
_gat_gtag_UA_1184911_1
Google uses this cookie to distinguish users.
1 Minute
Social Media Cookies
In some circumstances, we work with third parties to provide certain services to our users such as additional features (including the ability to see videos on our Sites) and to connect to certain social networks. These third parties use Cookies to collect information on our Sites, including via plug-ins and widgets. Some of these Cookies are persistent Cookies which remain on your computer or other Internet-connected device for a certain period of time after you end your browsing session, unless you delete them.
The privacy practices of these third parties, including Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, Vimeo and LinkedIn are subject to the privacy statements of such third parties, which are available here:
Facebook
Instagram
Twitter
Vimeo
LinkedIn
ShareThis
The following social media Cookies are used on our Sites:
Name of Cookie
Purpose of Use
Duration
NA
NA
NA
Your Choices
You can indicate your choice with respect to the use of Cookies via the Cookie preferences center tab available on the left side of the screen. Please note that, depending on your selection, you may not be able to take full advantage of the Sites or our products and services. In addition, you can also stop Cookies from being downloaded on your computer by selecting the appropriate settings on your web browser. Most web browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new Cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new Cookie and how to disable existing Cookies. On Microsoft Internet Explorer, this can be done by selecting “Tools/Internet Options” and reviewing your privacy settings or selecting “delete Cookies.” You can find out how to do this for your particular browser by clicking “help” on your browser’s menu or by visiting www.allaboutcookies.org. For mobile devices, you can manage how your device and browser share certain device data by adjusting the privacy and security settings on your mobile device.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Cookie Policy, please contact us by e-mail at: privacy@siegelgale.com.
COOKIE BANNER & PREFERENCES CENTRE
We use cookies that are necessary [to operate the website and provide you with the functionalities you requested]. With your permission, we would also like to use cookies, including third-party cookies,to [gather website analytics and statistics, such as via feedback polls, to improve your experience and to provide you with additional features (such as social media features)]
You can revisit your consent choices at any time by returning to this preference centreand find out more about cookies by visiting our Cookie Policy.
We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking "Accept and Close”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies. Read MoreACCEPT & CLOSEPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
